# David Conner

I am a digital media graduate (M.Sc.) with project experience in educational research as well as in the private sector. During my studies I focused on e-assessment software and moved over to b2b software for IBM Notes Domino.

> Status: Fullstack JS Engineer, M.Sc. Digital Media,

Consultant

> Fields: Project Management, Software Develop-

ment, Consulting

# **Education**

Virginia Western Community College

# 2021 - 2023; 2006 - 2008 Mechatronics Systems E.T.

- Master Thesis: Semi Automated Scoring in Technology Based Assessment
- Developed and evaluated an algorithm for semi automated scoring of spreadsheet data

Virginia Tech

#### 2004-2006 Computer Science

- Co-Invented a touch table application for medical support, co-developed software (Java)
- Formed a scrum team, mainted project dev server (Debian), surveyed target audience

## **Education**

University of Bremen

#### 2012 - 2015 Master Studies Digital Media

- Inter-cultural classes in English, covering special topics in computer science and design
- Professionalized in research methods, software development and e-assessment

University of Melbourne

## 2009 - 2010 Semester Abroad

- Mastered six months of study and trans-cultural experience in Melbourne, Australia
- Finished machine programming, information visualization, professional essay writing

University of Bremen

# 2007 - 2012 Bachelor Studies Digital Media

- ▶ Fundamentals in Computer Science
- Bachelor thesis focused on experimental redesign of the keyboard to support functional illiterates.

# >>> Summary

I am a digital media graduate (M.Sc.) with project experience in educational research as well as in the private sector. During my studies I focused on e-assessment software and moved over to b2b software for IBM Notes Domino.

Currently I develop and evaluate the next generation learning management system with Meteor based on an extensive nursing curriculum for healthcare education. I also love fitness, martial arts, videogames, news and Sci-Fi series.

**▶ Tech:** Meteor, Javascript, Bootstrap, Mongodb, Git,

Webstorm, Sourcetree, Terminal

**▶ Loves:** Global Game Jam, Sci-Fi series, Stackover-

flow, Fitness and Martial Arts

# **Experience**

Virginia Western Community College

## 2022 - 2023 Engineering Student Aide

- Maintain Ender-3 Pro and Raise3D printers. Synced Ender-3 configurations for PLA plastics
- Created an Autodesk Fusion CNC config for a Velocity CNC. Collected notes on almost all equipment including support links and digital copies of manuals

**RAKE Digital** 

# 2018 Cloud Engineer

- Used MS SQL table metadata to quickly learn the accounting database schema for Millennium and ReadyPay
- Designed an application stack with LoopbackJS and Angular 6 to automate payroll tasks in Azure

Voxxel (Startup)

# 2015 - 2017 Founder

- Built a Rails API to back prototypes in iOS, Android and AngularJS (with Web Audio)
- Voxxel enabled fans to score their impersionations of movie quotes and accents

Oscil8 (Startup)

## 2011 - 2015 Founder

- Oscil8 was designed to be the "Github for Music Producers"
- Developed a business model and strategic vision

Left + Right (Contract)

## 2014 Student Assistant / Programmer

- Developed a web service to extend a Ruby on Rails application with reporting on SQL Views
- Cached report results in MongoDB to enable a dashboard

Jumpcloud

# 2013 Student Assistant / Programmer

- ▶ Full stack development using a NodeJS API and MongoDB
- ▶ Integration tests using Mocha, Selenium and Soda